

BOYD Stacken

MARKETING

ECOMMERCE | WEB DEVELOPMENT

ANALYTICS | GRAPHIC DESIGN

SALES | COMMUNICATION

CONTACT

- (715) 245-3456
- 766 Magoo Rd.
 Hudson, WI 54016

PRO SKILLS

- Innovative Thinking
- Effective Communicator
- Analytical & Results Driven
- · Collaborative & Independent
- · Customer-first Perspective
- Online Reputation Management
 - CRM Management
- · Email & Direct Mail Marketing
- Adobe Lightroom, Illustrator & Photoshop
 - SEO & Content Optimization

ABOUT ME

Experienced Marketing & Sales Professional driven to be a part of a market-leading organization that stands behind their products and services while delivering a custom-er-first experience. With hands-on integration of marketing, sales, customer reputation management, and communication, I've had the opportunity to be a part of success and want to share that with a company while utilizing my full potential. I believe my past experiences and skill sets can contribute to the company's enduring success.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | COMMUNICATION STUDIES

University of Wisconsin - River Falls

WORK EXPERIENCE

ECOMMERCE MARKETING & OPTIMIZATION MANAGER

• 645 Hale Ave N. Oakdale, MN 55128

Comply Foam | April 2022 - Current

- Drive performance and optimization of the product merchandising and detail pages
- Develop and manage KPI's/metrics, utilize analytics to report on the performance across e-commerce efforts, glean insights and share findings with key stakeholders
- Support new product launches and promotional campaigns by developing product listings, including asset and content development while meeting agreed-upon timelines.
- Closely monitor customer needs, site performance & trends to develop, deliver, and main best-in-class site experiences utilizing connected applications, improving user interface/user
- Analyze, evaluate, and shift digital marketing campaigns, shopping trends, and competitive landscape to drive increased customer acquisitions (reach/ impressions), and conversions, and meet revenue goals
- Utilize SEO tools and PPC ads, understand competitors' presence in the marketplace and deploy keywords, advertising to spend efficiently (ROI) and maximize online performance (ROAS).
- Work with E-Commerce Marketing & Sales Manager to build the strategy, align creative goals, and develop the plan that includes email/SMS, social media, and digital marketing campaigns, and includes customer engagement (i.e. influencer program, blogs, etc.) while maintaining budget and forecast alignment.

REGIONAL MARKETING MANAGER SERVICE SALES MANAGER

N8232 945th St. River Falls, WI 54022

Green Oasis | May 2016 - April 2022

- Grow customer count in all services & monitor new sales and cancel rates regularly
- Train and manage inside/outside service sales staff
- · Create and manage and track inside sales campaigns
- Monitor and Implement up-sell opportunities using automated systems & processes
- Enhance and manage online reviews to positively reflect company reputation
- Implement efficient communication models to strengthen customers' experiences
- \bullet Provide valuable & relevant content to increase credibility and client engagement
- Design and plan email & direct mail campaigns for sales & educational purposes
- Showcase projects & community involvement through Social Media Platforms
- Trade show coordination and execution to establish new leads & potential clients
 Update website content to improve the user experience and utilize for SEO ranking
- Execute sweepstakes, contests, & sponsorships to engage with local communities